Guide to the Harland Bartholomew and Associates planning reports, 1944-1990.
Harland Bartholomew and Associates planning reports
- Land Use Plan, Kansas Street Urban Renewal, Area Tenn. A 11-2 [Memphis, Tennessee], 1972 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Memphis Downtown Area Parking Study: Justice Complex, Volunteer Park [Memphis and Shelby County, Tennessee], 1979 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- A Transportation Plan For The Memphis Urban Area [Tennessee], 1968 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Memphis Urban Area Transportation Study [Tennessee], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- [St. Jude’s Hospital and Interstate I-40, Memphis Tennessee], 1964 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Draft Environmental Impact Statement And Route Location Report, Northwest County Highway, Shelby County, Tennessee, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Walnut Grove Woods, Memphis, Shelby County, Tennessee, Final Environmental Impact Statement, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Whitehaven Levi Planning District Study [Memphis, Tennessee], 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Franconia-Springfield Area Plan [Virginia], 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Town of Herndon, Virginia, Herndon 2010 Comprehensive Plan, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
- Development Plan For Duwamish And Lower Green River Valley [City Of Seattle, King County, Port Of Seattle, Washington], 1954 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Land Use Plan, Spokane, Washington, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Needs And Resources For Improving Spokane [Washington}, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Parks And Open Spaces Plan, Spokane, Washington, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Program For Improving Spokane [Washington], 1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Sewerage Facilities Plan, Spokane, Washington, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Water Facilities Plan, Spokane, Washington, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Development Plan For The Port Of Tacoma Industrial District [Washington], 1955 (Box 7, Folder 12)